Committee on Student Life Records UA077
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Committee on Student Life Records
1968 -- 2016
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Arts and Sciences
Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty)
UA077
1.45 Linear Feet 2 boxes
14 Digital Object(s)
This collection contains the records of the Committee on Student Life.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Committee on Student Life, 2008-2016.
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series: Committee on Student Life.
Custodial History
Older records were found in the Ballou Hall Basement Vault. They appear to have come from the Office of Judicial Affairs, and were managed by Veronica Carter.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains reports, minutes, newspaper clippings, forms, and other documentation of the Committee on Student Life.
Student life; Curriculum and Instruction -- Faculty; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations; Student activism
- Committee on Student Life Records, 1968 -- 2016; UA077.001; 1.45 Linear Feet; 14 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains minutes, reports, and other documentation of the Committee on Student Life.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in order of accession.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2003; UA077.001.003.00001; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .03 Megabytes
    Open for research.
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2002-2003
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by the Student Life Committee, 2016, accession 2017.028.
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2004; UA077.001.003.00002; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .07 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2003-2004
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2005; UA077.001.003.00003; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .04 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2004-2005
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2006; UA077.001.003.00004; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .08 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2005-2006
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2007; UA077.001.003.00005; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .09 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2006-2007
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2008; UA077.001.003.00006; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .17 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2007-2008
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2009; UA077.001.003.00007; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .13 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2008-2009
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2010; UA077.001.003.00008; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .13 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2009-2010
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2011; UA077.001.003.00009; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .13 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2010-2011
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2012; UA077.001.003.00010; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .09 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2011-2012
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2013; UA077.001.003.00011; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .08 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2012-2013
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2014; UA077.001.003.00012; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .13 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2013-2014
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2015; UA077.001.003.00013; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .15 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2014-2015
  - Committee on Student Life annual report, 2016; UA077.001.003.00014; Student Life Committee (AS&E Faculty); 1 Digital Object(s); .38 Megabytes
    Committee on Student Life annual report 2015-2016
  - Minutes, September 25, 2000; UA077.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Minutes, October 6, 2000; UA077.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Subcommittee minutes, November 3, 2000; UA077.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, November 3, 2000; UA077.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, November 17, 2000; UA077.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, December 1, 2000; UA077.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, April 20, 2001; UA077.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Hearing on Severity of Punishment, February 26, 2004; UA077.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, November 12, 2004; UA077.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, October 6, 2007; UA077.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, October 26, 2007; UA077.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - CSL-Current, 1979 -- 1981; UA077.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Football, 1978; UA077.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - CSL- Annual Report, 1970 -- 1979; UA077.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - CSL, 1970 -- 1971; UA077.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - CSL, 1971 -- 1972; UA077.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - CSL, 1972 -- 1973; UA077.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - CSL, 1975; UA077.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - CSL, 1977 -- 1978; UA077.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - CSL, 1978 -- 1979; UA077.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Academic Standing, 1977 -- 1978; UA077.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Student Life, 1968 -- 1970; UA077.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Disciplinary Procedures, 1978 -- 1979; UA077.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Disciplinary Procedures, 1968; UA077.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Discipline, 1976 -- 1977; UA077.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Dormitory Autonomy, 1968 -- 1978; UA077.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - CSL- Dorm Security, 1973 -- 1974; UA077.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - CSL- Dorm Security, 1978; UA077.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Financial Aid and CSL Policy, 1973 -- 1979; UA077.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1976; UA077.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School, 1978; UA077.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Health Services, 1977; UA077.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Minutes Fall, 1979 -- 1980; UA077.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Minutes, 1978 -- 1979; UA077.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Minutes, 1977 -- 1978; UA077.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Minutes, 1975 -- 1978; UA077.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous CSL, 1976 -- 1977; UA077.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous CSL, 1975 -- 1976; UA077.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous CSL, 1977 -- 1979; UA077.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - CSL- Policy, 1978 -- 1979; UA077.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Previous Minutes, 1969 -- 1975; UA077.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Observer Clippings, 1974 -- 1976; UA077.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Organization Forms (Student), 1975 -- 1980; UA077.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Subcommittee on Racism- CSL, 1977; UA077.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Residential Life, 1974 -- 1976; UA077.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Snowballing Incident, 1975 -- 1976; UA077.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Wendell Phillips Awards, 1976 -- 1979; UA077.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - 1978/79 Student Organization Approved/Disaproved, 1978 -- 1979; UA077.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Student Organization, 1977 -- 1978; UA077.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Student Organization, 1976 -- 1977; UA077.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Student Organization, 1975 -- 1976; UA077.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - CSL-Term Papers, 1972 -- 1973; UA077.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Title IX, 1975 -- 1976; UA077.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Title IX, 1976 -- 1977; UA077.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Traffic Commission, 1978; UA077.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Student Enterprises (TSE), 1969; UA077.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - Vending Machine, 1969 -- 1974; UA077.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - CSL [1 of 2], 1976 -- 1979; UA077.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - CSL [2 of 2], 1977 -- 1978; UA077.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - [Student Disciplinary Procedures], 1977 -- 1978; UA077.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
  - Notification of Privacy Rights, 1977; UA077.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - [Host Advisor Application], 1983; UA077.001.002.00051 (Box 2)